mssqltips.com 2019-08-24

# MSSQLTips - Privacy

MSSQLTips.com respects your privacy and the personal data that we collect from you as a best practice and to comply with General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) going into effect on May 25, 2018. In order to provide the necessary information to serve your needs, we may request personal information from you. The information collected and how it is used will vary across the site. This policy is our way of letting you know how we collect information, what we collect it for, and what choices you may have. 

MSSQLTips.com also provides links to other sites we believe may be of interest to you. These sites are provided as a convenience and are beyond our control. You are advised to check the privacy policies of those sites before providing your personal information to them. 

## Types Of Data Collection

MSSQLTips.com collects only your email address for the mailing list which is the daily newsletter and sponsored newsletter.  Other information including name, phone number, mailing address, company, etc. may be collected for special features such as whitepapers, webinars, contests, etc.

##  Data Automatically Collected

MSSQLTips.com may use cookies, web analytics, or other technologies to automatically collect certain information about you when you visit our website. Please note, these may be first party cookies or tools or third party cookies or tools, which are hosted by another party.

##  Tip and Tutorial Comments

Any information that you may disclose on community forums or other public areas of MSSQLTips.com becomes public information, and you are solely responsible for your contributions.

## How Data Is Used

The data collected and stored in the United States for the purpose of sending out the daily newsletter and sponsored newsletter.  In addition, the data may be used to send out periodic emails updating you about other SQL Server offerings.  The data is not shared or sold to any other company except with our Sponsors as noted on the forms.

At the current time, all content on the website is free and does not require a login.  Other offers such as whitepapers, webinars, contests, etc. may require you to enter personal data at the time of download or registration.  This data will be shared with our sponsors, so if you do not wish for your personal data to be shared, please do not complete the forms.

## Opt-out

You may opt-out of receiving email updates at any time by sending an email to [ unsubscribe@mssqltips.com](mailto:unsubscribe@mssqltips.com?subject=Unsubscribe) with a subject of "Unsubscribe" or use the unsubscribe option at the bottom of every email that is sent.

## Children under the Age of 18

MSSQLTips.com is not intended for children under the age of 18. No one under age 18 may provide any personal information. MSSQLTips.com does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If you are under 18, please do not register for anything.

## Compliance Issues

Should you believe your personal information has been used in a way that is not consistent with this policy or your stated preferences, or should you have further questions related to this policy, please contact Greg Robidoux at [gregr@edgewoodsolutions.com](mailto:gregr@edgewoodsolutions.com) or call 1-603-566-4928. 

Written inquiries may be addressed to Edgewood Solutions c/o Greg Robidoux, P.O. Box 682, Wilton, NH, USA 03086.

## Policy Updates

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any changes in our privacy practices that affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our website notifying users of the change. In some cases we will also email users who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

We may update this policy from time to time to describe how new site features affect our use of your information and to let you know of new control and preference features that we provide you. 

If you have questions about our Privacy Statement, please e-mail us at [privacy@mssqltips.com](mailto:privacy@mssqltips.com).

updated: 2018-05-22

* * *

* * *

Copyright (c) 2006-2019 [Edgewood Solutions, LLC](https://www.edgewoodsolutions.com/) All rights reserved  
Some names and products listed are the registered trademarks of their respective owners.
